Rise up!
Are you there?
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I am preparing you to receive healing
in the name of Jesus!
I am preparing you to receive
deliverance in the name of Jesus!
To receive blessing in the name of Jesus!
Every dry bone, rise again.
Viewers at home, wherever you are,
whatever you are doing right now, viewers,
you are here, we are there!
Begin to say, "Thank You, Jesus".
Say, Out of this body, you evil spirit, in the name of Jesus!
Out of this life, you evil spirit, you demon, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
I command that devil in your temple, body - hands of sickness, disease and affliction,
you devil, out of this body!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
The kingdom of darkness is in disarray right now as people are manifesting.
The demons inside of them are right now manifesting because of the fire of the Holy Spirit.
In the name of Jesus!
Do you know what it means?
If the devil is out of your body, disease, failure and setback is out of your life.
When we say, "out of this body", we mean, we separate everything that causes you pain, discomfort.
I say, Out of this body!
I say, Out of this life, you devil, affliction, disease, setback!
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Who are you?
I am the destroyer!
I am destroying their lives.
I am finishing her children.
They are suffering, I destroy them.
I want to finish them.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
It is possible to separate your past from you.
Your past is failure and affliction,
Do you believe that?
I command that devil, affliction - out of your body!
I say, Out of your body!
Out of your blood!
Out of your kidneys!
Out of your liver!
Out of your bones!
Out of your tendons!
I say, out of your body!
I cant hear you! Say, Out of my body!
Out of my blood, you devil!
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You can still see people vomiting out strange substances from their system -
poison that they have been eating for so long from the table of the enemy.
The Spirit of God Almighty is flushing them out right now so continue to pray.
She is my wife.
Everybody hates her.
- Her career?
- Which career?
I said, Everybody hates her - which career?
- What have you done to her?
- She is my wife.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
In the name of Jesus, all knees shall bow!
I separate you from sickness,
affliction; be separated!
I separate you from affliction, disease!
Your bones - be separated!
Your blood - be separated!
Your kidneys - be separated!
Your liver - be separated!
I say, Be separated!
I cant hear you - be separated!
Be separated!
The Spirit of God is working within and outside you.
Right now, exploit it and get well!
Get well; get delivered!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen and still see people vomiting out the poisonous substances in their system -
strange substances, poison that they have eaten from the table of the enemy.
Right now, the Spirit of the living
God is setting them free.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Be healed!
Wherever that affliction is, you are asked to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
The right hand of God is power.
Begin to touch that affected part.
Wherever you have that pain, confess God's Word over your sickness and situation.
Watch your screen.
See the strange substance.
Who are you?
I am a lion; we are many.
I destroyed him; I deported him back to Nigeria.
To come and kill him.
Move like a lion!
Command them out!
You affliction - out!
Say, Affliction - out!
Prayer!
Say, Out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Be in an attitude of prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus Christ!
With all your heart say, Thank You, Jesus!
Confess your healing and freedom.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Right now, begin to cover your way with
the blood of Jesus.
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Ask for a new dawn!
Your business - Good Morning!
Greet your career, way, Good Morning, in the name of Jesus!
They are new every morning.
Good Morning, my career, future, finances!
Good Morning!
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
I cover your way, career, life, family,
direction and focus with the blood of Jesus.
Cover them with the blood of Jesus, in Jesus Christ's name!
Happy New Beginning!
Right now, begin to walk in new beginning - walk, talk and reason new!
Believe with all your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I'm starting a new beginning!
Now, it is time to talk, think victory!
Old things have passed away!
You have started it here!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbour, The
Lord is your strength.
I have started today -
a new beginning.
The Lord is my strength.
Greet your neighbour.
The heart that believes
will enjoy a new beginning.
A new beginning is a victor.
The heart that believes
a new beginning.
Your heart believes - rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
If God is your strength, it will happen.
If it's not by your effort, but it will happen.
It's by the grace of God a new beginning!
Do you believe?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Believing is the only condition for answered prayers
With my mouth I confess, with my heart I believe
I believe God's Word is true for my life
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You have overcome your unbelief.
Say, I have overcome my unbelief.
If you have overcome, the message is for you.
The word of God is true for your life.
So now, you look, smile, reason differently.
So your attitude is nowadays quite different because you have started a new beginning.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The life that you have started - God is your strength.
That is why you will not understand.
It's not your strength.
You have ended your own strength and God's strength has started.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Your strength is past, and God's strength is now.
Hallelujah!
How to maintain this strength - God's strength - the Word of God is the answer.
To maintain the blessing, the victory
you have received is by the Word of God.
The only way is through the Word of God.
Meditate on it, and the revelation will come, The strength will continue.
I see you maintaining God's strength!
I see you maintaining a new beginning!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
I am rejoicing in your new beginning.
I am rejoicing for you!
Every impossibibility becomes possible right now because of God's strength.
With God, all things are possible.
I am prophesying to your life.
This is the Word of God for you:
I see you maintaining your new beginning!
In your new beginning, defeat and failure are the things of the past!
This is decreed.
The new beginning you have started today, defeat and failure are the things of the past!
You can count how many defeats and failures you have had in the past.
They are things of the past.
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer